

5407 Rushmere Court 248-275-9593 angelagola.ko@gmail.com

Full-Stack Engineer with a business management degree. Completion of Certificate in Full Stack Web Development from Michigan State University early September. Solutions Analyst for Oracle-Cerner. High attention to detail with a desire to contribute to and create efficient processes. My past experiences and motivation to learn new technology ensures reliable and timely delivery of projects.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, SASS, React, Node.js, Express.js, APIs, MongoDB, Bootstrap, SQL, Sequelize, Handlebars

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Oracle-Cerner**, Remote — Solutions Analyst

FEB 2022 - PRESENT

Provide Tier 1 phone support troubleshooting citrix receiver connections, login issues, freezing, application workflows, displays, and further triaging to various support teams.

### **Vail Resorts**, Vail, CO — Events & Operations Manager.

OCT 2018- JAN 2021

Increase sales, coordinate with vendors, event orders, inventory, ordering, scheduling, oversee 30+ employees, POS, OpenTable, Excel, Microsoft, opening/closing, restaurant management.

## **Xanterra**, Yellowstone NP — Food & Beverage Manager

MAR 2018 - OCT 2018 - Seasonal

Open/Close, ordering, scheduling, oversee 30+ employees, POS, Microsoft, Excel, Kronos, budgeting, sales, employee retention, hiring, customer service.

### Cannonsburg Ski Area, Belmont, MI — Assistant Food & Beverage Manager

SEP 2017 - MAR 2017 - Seasonal

Open/Close, bartending, scheduling, POS, Microsoft, Excel, customer service.

### **WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS**

# Travelot | https://github.com/angelagola-ko/Travelot-Destination-Planner | https://travelot-app.herokuapp.com

Description: Makes travel planning easier. Search for destinations and receive information on the top rated nearby attractions, add destinations to your Wish List, and reminisce past memories by adding to your past trips library.

Role: Past Trips page and design. Past Trips page includes functionality for cards and API.

Technologies: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Handlebars, Sequelize, API, mySQL

# Vocab Builder | https://github.com/angelagola-ko/vocabBuilder | https://angelagola-ko.github.io/vocabBuilder

Description: An application introducing new vocabulary words, generating random words from a list of 900+ advanced words outputting definition, as well as translation in Spanish with ability to add/remove words from local storage.

Role: API function, function for displaying words, design.

Technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, Bulma, API

# Code Quiz | https://github.com/angelagola-ko/code-quiz | https://angelagola-ko.github.io/code-quiz/index.html

Description: A quiz created in JavaScript.

Role: Built from scratch.

Technologies: JavaScript, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS

### **EDUCATION**

## Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI — Certificate

MARCH 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Fullstack Web Development

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

# Red Rocks Community College, Lakewood, CO — Non-Degree

AUG 2020 - AUG 2021 - Intro to Python, Statistics, Chemistry, Bio-Chem

# **Grand Valley State University**, Grand Rapids, MI — Bachelors

MAY 2013 - MAY 2017

Hospitality Management and Tourism